<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>

    <!-- Shared head assets for legal pages -->
    <template id="legal_page_head">
        <t t-call="bhukhadan_web.seo_head"/>
        <link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css"
              t-attf-href="/bhukhadan_web/static/src/css/bhuarjan_website.css?v=18.0.1.2.3"/>
        <link rel="stylesheet"
              href="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/font-awesome/6.5.0/css/all.min.css"/>
        <link href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css2?family=Plus+Jakarta+Sans:wght@400;500;600;700;800&amp;display=swap"
              rel="stylesheet"/>
    </template>

    <!-- Paytm-style tab navigation -->
    <template id="legal_nav_tabs" name="BhuKhadan Legal Navigation">
        <nav class="bhu-legal-tabs" aria-label="Legal documents">
            <a t-attf-class="bhu-legal-tab #{active_tab == 'terms' and 'active' or ''}"
               href="/terms-and-conditions">Terms &amp; Conditions</a>
            <a t-attf-class="bhu-legal-tab #{active_tab == 'privacy' and 'active' or ''}"
               href="/privacy-policy">Privacy Policy</a>
            <a t-attf-class="bhu-legal-tab #{active_tab == 'cookies' and 'active' or ''}"
               href="/cookie-policy">Cookie Policy</a>
        </nav>
    </template>

    <!-- Payment disclaimer (reused on privacy page) -->
    <template id="payment_disclaimer_body" name="BhuKhadan Payment Disclaimer">
        <h2 class="bhu-legal-subtitle">Disclaimer Regarding Payment Processing and Liability</h2>
        <p>
            The <strong>BhuKhadan</strong> application is a software platform developed and maintained by
            <strong>REDMELON BUSINESS SOLUTIONS PRIVATE LIMITED</strong> (&quot;REDMELON&quot;) solely for the purpose of
            facilitating digital processing, workflow management, record keeping, and payment administration
            activities as configured by the concerned Department/Authority.
        </p>
        <p>
            All payment-related information, including but not limited to beneficiary details, ownership records,
            bank account information, compensation amounts, award calculations, approvals, and payment authorizations,
            are entered, verified, approved, and processed by authorized officials of the concerned
            Department/Authority.
        </p>
        <p>
            REDMELON does not verify, validate, audit, certify, or guarantee the accuracy, completeness,
            authenticity, or legality of any data entered into the system by users. The responsibility for ensuring
            the correctness of beneficiary details, payment amounts, ownership records, and all related approvals
            rests exclusively with the concerned Department/Authority and its authorized users.
        </p>
        <p>
            REDMELON shall not be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, consequential, financial, legal, or
            administrative loss, damage, claim, dispute, recovery proceeding, excess payment, short payment,
            duplicate payment, erroneous payment, fraudulent payment, or payment made to an incorrect beneficiary
            arising from or related to the use of the application, incorrect data entry, improper verification,
            unauthorized access, user error, or departmental decisions.
        </p>
        <p>
            By using the BhuKhadan application, the Department/Authority acknowledges and agrees that all payment
            approvals and disbursements are undertaken at its sole responsibility and risk. The Department/Authority
            shall remain solely responsible for compliance with all applicable laws, rules, notifications, financial
            regulations, audit requirements, and departmental procedures governing such payments.
        </p>
        <p>
            REDMELON acts only as a technology service provider and shall not be considered a party to any payment
            transaction, compensation determination, ownership verification process, or beneficiary entitlement
            decision conducted through the application.
        </p>
    </template>

    <!-- ============================================================
         TERMS & CONDITIONS PAGE
         ============================================================ -->
    <template id="terms_and_conditions_page" name="BhuKhadan – Terms &amp; Conditions">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <t t-set="additional_title">Terms &amp; Conditions</t>
            <t t-set="meta_description">BhuKhadan Terms &amp; Conditions — platform usage, responsibilities, and service terms for the land acquisition management system by REDMELON BUSINESS SOLUTIONS PRIVATE LIMITED.</t>
            <t t-set="bhu_page_keywords" t-value="'BhuKhadan terms and conditions, REDMELON BUSINESS SOLUTIONS PRIVATE LIMITED, land acquisition platform, legal'"/>
            <t t-set="no_header" t-value="1"/>
            <t t-set="no_footer" t-value="1"/>
            <t t-set="head">
                <t t-call="bhukhadan_web.legal_page_head"/>
            </t>

            <t t-call="bhukhadan_web.navbar"/>

            <div class="bhu-legal-page">
                <t t-set="active_tab" t-value="'terms'"/>
                <t t-call="bhukhadan_web.legal_nav_tabs"/>

                <div class="bhu-legal-content">
                    <h1 class="bhu-legal-title">BhuKhadan Terms &amp; Conditions</h1>

                    <h2 class="bhu-legal-subtitle">Use of the BhuKhadan Platform</h2>
                    <p>
                        These Terms &amp; Conditions (&quot;Terms&quot;) govern access to and use of the
                        <strong>BhuKhadan</strong> land acquisition management platform, website, and related services
                        (collectively, the &quot;Platform&quot;) provided by
                        <strong>REDMELON BUSINESS SOLUTIONS PRIVATE LIMITED</strong> (&quot;REDMELON&quot;, &quot;we&quot;, &quot;us&quot;).
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        The Platform is licensed to and operated for the concerned <strong>Department/Authority</strong>
                        and its authorized officials. By accessing or using the Platform, you confirm that you are an
                        authorized user and agree to these Terms.
                    </p>

                    <h2 class="bhu-legal-subtitle">Platform Role &amp; Responsibilities</h2>
                    <p>
                        BhuKhadan is a technology platform for workflow management, documentation, approvals, and
                        payment administration as configured by the Department/Authority. REDMELON provides software
                        infrastructure, maintenance, and support as a <strong>technology service provider only</strong>.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        All statutory decisions, verifications, approvals, compensation determinations, and payment
                        authorizations remain the sole responsibility of the Department/Authority and its designated
                        officials. REDMELON does not act as a party to land acquisition proceedings or payment
                        transactions.
                    </p>

                    <h2 class="bhu-legal-subtitle">User Obligations</h2>
                    <p>
                        Authorized users must maintain the confidentiality of login credentials, enter accurate data,
                        follow applicable laws and departmental procedures, and use the Platform only for official
                        purposes. Unauthorized access, data tampering, or misuse of the Platform is prohibited.
                    </p>

                    <h2 class="bhu-legal-subtitle">Payment Processing</h2>
                    <p>
                        Payment-related disclaimers and liability limitations are set out in our
                        <a href="/privacy-policy">Privacy Policy</a>, including the
                        <em>Disclaimer Regarding Payment Processing and Liability</em>. By using payment features of
                        the Platform, you acknowledge those terms.
                    </p>

                    <h2 class="bhu-legal-subtitle">Intellectual Property</h2>
                    <p>
                        The Platform, including its software, design, documentation, and branding, is owned by REDMELON BUSINESS SOLUTIONS PRIVATE LIMITED
                        or its licensors. No rights are granted except as necessary for authorized use under the
                        applicable service agreement with the Department/Authority.
                    </p>

                    <h2 class="bhu-legal-subtitle">Limitation of Liability</h2>
                    <p>
                        To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, REDMELON shall not be liable for losses
                        arising from incorrect user data entry, departmental decisions, third-party integrations,
                        network interruptions, or events beyond reasonable control. See the Privacy Policy for
                        payment-specific liability terms.
                    </p>

                    <h2 class="bhu-legal-subtitle">Changes &amp; Contact</h2>
                    <p>
                        REDMELON may update these Terms from time to time. Continued use of the Platform after updates
                        constitutes acceptance of the revised Terms. For questions, contact
                        <a href="mailto:support@bhuarjan.com">support@bhuarjan.com</a>.
                    </p>

                    <p class="bhu-legal-meta">
                        Platform developed and maintained by
                        <a href="https://www.redmelon.co.in" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">REDMELON BUSINESS SOLUTIONS PRIVATE LIMITED</a>
                        (REDMELON BUSINESS SOLUTIONS PRIVATE LIMITED).
                    </p>
                </div>
            </div>

            <t t-call="bhukhadan_web.footer"/>
        </t>
    </template>

    <!-- ============================================================
         PRIVACY POLICY PAGE
         ============================================================ -->
    <template id="privacy_policy_page" name="BhuKhadan – Privacy Policy">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <t t-set="additional_title">Privacy Policy</t>
            <t t-set="meta_description">BhuKhadan Privacy Policy — data handling, payment processing disclaimer, and liability terms for the land acquisition platform by REDMELON BUSINESS SOLUTIONS PRIVATE LIMITED.</t>
            <t t-set="bhu_page_keywords" t-value="'BhuKhadan privacy policy, payment disclaimer, REDMELON BUSINESS SOLUTIONS PRIVATE LIMITED, land acquisition'"/>
            <t t-set="no_header" t-value="1"/>
            <t t-set="no_footer" t-value="1"/>
            <t t-set="head">
                <t t-call="bhukhadan_web.legal_page_head"/>
            </t>

            <t t-call="bhukhadan_web.navbar"/>

            <div class="bhu-legal-page">
                <t t-set="active_tab" t-value="'privacy'"/>
                <t t-call="bhukhadan_web.legal_nav_tabs"/>

                <div class="bhu-legal-content">
                    <h1 class="bhu-legal-title">BhuKhadan Privacy Policy</h1>

                    <h2 class="bhu-legal-subtitle">Overview</h2>
                    <p>
                        This Privacy Policy describes how <strong>REDMELON BUSINESS SOLUTIONS PRIVATE LIMITED</strong>
                        (&quot;REDMELON BUSINESS SOLUTIONS PRIVATE LIMITED&quot;, &quot;REDMELON&quot;, &quot;we&quot;) handles information in
                        connection with the <strong>BhuKhadan</strong> platform operated for the concerned
                        Department/Authority. Official land records, beneficiary data, and payment information are
                        entered and controlled by authorized government users.
                    </p>

                    <t t-call="bhukhadan_web.payment_disclaimer_body"/>

                    <h2 class="bhu-legal-subtitle">Data Security</h2>
                    <p>
                        We implement industry-standard technical and organizational measures to protect platform
                        availability and security. Access is restricted to authenticated users authorized by the
                        Department/Authority.
                    </p>

                    <h2 class="bhu-legal-subtitle">Contact</h2>
                    <p>
                        For privacy-related enquiries, email
                        <a href="mailto:support@bhuarjan.com">support@bhuarjan.com</a>
                        or visit our <a href="/contact">contact page</a>.
                    </p>

                    <p class="bhu-legal-meta">
                        Platform developed and maintained by
                        <a href="https://www.redmelon.co.in" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">REDMELON BUSINESS SOLUTIONS PRIVATE LIMITED</a>
                        (REDMELON BUSINESS SOLUTIONS PRIVATE LIMITED).
                    </p>
                </div>
            </div>

            <t t-call="bhukhadan_web.footer"/>
        </t>
    </template>

</odoo>
